<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Cents</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Search</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="state_text_view">Select State</string>
    <string name="city_text_view">Select City</string>
    <string name="occupation_text_view">Enter Occupation</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submission Button</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job_list">Job Listings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cost_of_living">Cost Of Living</string>
    <string name="title_activity_spending_breakdown">SpendingBreakdown</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab_host">Search Results</string>
    <string name="title_activity_job_detail">Job Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search">Cents</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_closed">Closed</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="col_explanation">Considering moving to a different location or do you want to know how your current city compares? Get cost of living information, tax information, average weather breakdown by month, and labor statistics for a specific city or compare two. </string>
    <string name="about">Cents is a financial decision engine; a way to help potential and current college students realize the impact of their educational and vocational choices. Cents has been built by acquiring information from prospective users, current academic advisors, and the best data sources on the Internet, which come together in a complete package to make it an easy-to-navigate and always accessible career guidance counselor.  Cents provides information, in a very intuitive way, that will allow users to prepare for their education, understand their career options, and visualize their future expenses.</string>
    <string name="spending_explanation">Want to compare your spending to the spending trends of others or do you want to setup a monthly budget? Create a spending breakdown that matches your needs here. </string>
    <string name="college_explanation">Researching potential schools, or do you want to see how your school stacks up? Compare tuition rates, undergrad enrollment rates and the school\'s graduation rate.</string>
    <string name="career_explanation">Want to see the job outlook for a career you are considering? Check in to see what your prospective careers have to offer in terms of salary, demand, and unemployment.</string>
    <string name="major_explanation">Curious to see what the top jobs are for what you are studying? or want to compare potential majors based on potential salaries, recommendations and satisfaction?</string>
    <string-array name="nav_array_logged_out">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Login</item>
        <item>Register</item>
        <item>Example</item>
        <item>Wizard</item>
        <item>About</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nav_array_logged_in">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Logout</item>
        <item>Profile</item>
        <item>Example</item>
        <item>Wizard</item>
        <item>About</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_visualization_pager">VisualizationPagerActivity</string>

</resources>
